question_data = [
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Gumbo is a stew that originated in Louisiana.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Bulls are attracted to the color red.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "&quot;27 Club&quot; is a term used to refer to a list of famous actors, musicians, and artists who died at the age of 27.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Dihydrogen Monoxide was banned due to health risks after being discovered in 1983 inside swimming pools and drinking water.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Scotland voted to become an independent country during the referendum from September 2014.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The National Animal of Scotland is the Unicorn.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
